

+085722105122

Propaganisa.reg@gmail.com

I am a hard-working programmer, who likes to learn many things, and has the experience of using a variety of technologies in IT. I have superior initiative and problem solvers, and are responsive. I also enjoy working both in teams and individually.

Experience

09/2015 to 05/2019

BANK BPR NCP – IT STAFF 2012-2013

- Developed application using ms access
- Managing company database using PostgreSQL.
- IT support job such as installing and configuring computer, repair printer, etc.

CV RC ELECTRONICS – DESKTOP PROGRAMMER 2014-2015

 Developed stock application for company based factory in Bandung and Jakarta using foxpro and MySQL database

PT INSAN INFONESIA – PROGRAMMER 2015-2018

- Developed application using PHP and MySQL
- Learning various things such as GIT, Phyton language,
 Api, Wiki, Putty, security programming, penetration testing.

Skill

- PHP
- Framework(Codelgniter, Laravel, Django,etc)
- Phyton(begginer)
- GIT versioning control
- Putty
- Familiar with various databases such as MySQL, PostgreSQL, Oracle, Mongodb,etc.
- RestAPI
- Familiar with linux
- Able to talk and read in English language(intermediate, score EPT 557)

Education

Bachelor of Information Technology - 2020 Widyatama University, BDG GPA 3,36

Hobbies

 Learning new things, reading books, learning language, etc.